So, what's stopping you from letting
your coding agent manage your
infrastructure? Seriously, why not give
it admin access to your AWS account and
just trust it to do the right thing?
Yeah. No, I didn't think so. So, this is
exactly the question I've been trying to
answer the past year working at
Stackback. And come meet me in New York
where we'll be talking about existing
security measures like command white
listing, container sandboxing, and why
this stuff is not enough if you want
your agent to run your infrastructure.
We're going to share research we've been
working on the past year for the first
time and I would love to take these
discussions in person. So yeah, see you
in New York.